PEDRO: Her name is Soledad.
I brought her.
'cause
we're gonna get married.
And I want to run
what we created.
I want to be
part of the family.
Well. you have to provide me
with absolutely pure cocaine
at prices that's
gonna make your balls hurt.
Who the fuck are you. man?
Doesn't matter who I am.
It only matters
who I represent.
And who's that?
The United States Government.
Shit. 5.000 ain't shit.
FRANKLIN:
It is. It's a lot.
I don't want those two
knowing what I'm holding.
(gunshots)
(screams)
Motherfucking Biscuit!
I told you not to mention
that fucking money!
Lucia Villanueva.
Tell your boss
we can help each other out.
Hey. what you looking for?
We got what you need. man.
Wait!
(screams)
Back the fuck up!
(gunshot)
(sputters)
FRANKLIN:
We've lost the buyer.
And I'm out of my supply.
What.
you're gonna take Avi's place?
I'd like to try.
You know. I'm starting
to realize
that you got one job
in this life.
and that's to protect
the people you love.
Get in here.
Oh my God!
-Oh. shit!
-Franklin!
(dog barking in distance)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(toilet flushes)
FRANKLIN:
I thought maybe I should go.
before your pop shoots me
for some burglar.
That's Jerome's idea
of being careful.
So...
You just in danger
walking down the street now?
Well. I carry
a lot cash sometimes.
(somber music)
Hey.
♪
How long we got?
An hour or two.
But if you hear something
that sound like the front door.
you best get your ass
out here fast.
♪
(engine turns over)
(police siren chirping rapidly)
♪
("Young Turks" by Rod Stewart)
♪ Billy left his home
with a dollar in his pocket ♪
♪ And a head full of dreams
(cheerful conversation)
TEDDY:
I hated that dog.
-I hated that dog!
MATT: Hated!
And I'm just like. what did
the dog do to you. man?
MATT:
That's a canine!
Every time you came home
at night with dad's car
-after getting all...
-That was with...
both: Margolis!
Oh. man.
And he's standing there.
4:00 in the morning.
-he's standing there...
-You're out here trying
to explain to him. you're like.
about health class and
hormones. and all kids gotta...
He's scared to death!
"It's all all right. man."
both:
(laughs)
"Be cool. Dad."
I got eyes on the LZ.
♪
All right. so yeah. this
is gonna be real professional.
It should just be two or three
low-level Colombian guys.
They probably
won't even speak English.
Just open the doors.
stand aside.
and let them load up the...
You told me 15 times already.
tell me once more.
I'm gonna crash this plane
into the desert.
All right. well.
it's not a joke. though.
We get in.
we get out. right?
That's affirmative.
Thank you.
-♪ Time. time. time
-♪ Time is on your side
♪ Is on your side. is on
your side. is on your side ♪
♪ Young hearts
be free tonight ♪
♪ Tonight. tonight. tonight.
tonight. tonight. yeah ♪
♪ Time is on your side
♪ Ooh. ooh
♪
(chickens squawk)
Shit.
Yeah.
Real professional.
like a couple of Green Berets
dropping in on a VC picnic.
Hola.
(speaking Spanish)
You will wait
for Danilo and Diego.
No. that's what I'm saying.
we don't have time for that.
We're gonna miss the window
for our drop.
Mm.
Search them.
(grunts)
Hey. man. that is not a weapon.
-This is ridiculous.
-(scoffs)
Whoa. whoa. all right.
all right. all right.
Look. we do this every week.
No. you did.
All right. you know what?
I want my cocaine
on that plane right now.
you understand me?
(ominous music)
(shouts)
What's wrong with you?
You know who we are?
♪
I'm sorry. do you not know
-who we are?
-(speaking Spanish)
♪
The bosses only need
one of you alive to talk.
♪
Mm... I'm supposed
to be back by morning.
Or at least call Jerome.
(moans)
(distant R&B music playing)
Your days of slaving for that
Jheri curl motherfucker
is over.
-Mm-mm.
-Seriously.
So... Ooh!
Come on!
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna take you out
for breakfast.
Mm-hmm.
And then bring you back.
And make you pass out again.
(moans)
(groans)
But I really gotta go!
Mm-mm.
♪
You don't understand
what this is about. do you?
♪
What do you mean?
Don't go anywhere.
Where you going?
♪
Open it.
Now you see what we're doing?
(squeals)
(ominous music)
♪
(speaking Spanish)
(man shouting in Spanish)
MIGUEL:
Tuscon. Loredo. El Paso.
Like a gypsy.
Cheap motels and trailer parks.
And the girl?
Soledad Caro.
Both parents dead.
no brothers or sisters.
She went to Galveston Community
College for a year.
and she was tending bar
at some shithole in El Paso
called El Hueco
when they met.
-You checked that out?
-Owner confirmed it.
Said she pretty much
ran the place for him.
(snorts)
A monkey could run a dive bar.
A trained monkey.
I guess I really only have
one other question for you.
How the hell did you miss this?
-What?
-Pedro!
You said it was
like he'd vanished.
He was smart.
he used only cash.
had fake IDs.
moved around a lot.
In Arizona and Texas.
(distant music playing)
♪
-Miguel.
-Pedro.
It's good to have you back.
-Lucia.
-(speaking Spanish)
I didn't know
you were coming by today.
We talked about a job.
Which I said I'd think about.
And have you?
What's the hurry?
You just got back.
Take her to Knotts Berry Farm.
We'll talk next week.
I want to work.
Yeah.
and I've wasted enough time.
The family business is as much
mine as it is yours. Lucia.
Now...
What do you have for us?
(romantic music playing)
Mm-mm. baby.
you're supposed to be on guard.
How are you gonna stop
a burglar if I'm on top of you?
-Was that Louie?
-Uh-uh. Jerome.
she ain't here.
Hey. what's she
doing here. Lee?
You supposed to be
on guard. man.
Hey. my nigga.
she keeping me up.
Where the hell you been?
Over at Claudia's.
Between the VSOP
and the tongue-lashin'.
I passed out. but I got here
as soon as I could.
For all I know.
you could be in trouble. right?
Uh-huh.
Lot of people
want what we got.
What you and Franklin got.
All I got is burnt fingers
and hair that smell like shit.
(screams)
Goddamnit. Jerome!
Why you got these niggas
all over my house?
We ain't running
no goddamn motel.
(chuckles)
-Hey. hold up...
-Delroy and them got killed!
-They cut off their dicks. man!
-Huh?
They cut
off their dicks. man!
-Mexicans! They cut off they...
-Who you talking about?
Delroy
and my little cousin. man!
They cut their dicks off.
you're sure?
Yeah. nigga. I'm sure.
Why you just standing here?
Get the heat.
we gotta ride on them!
Guns for what?
What you think?
Kill us some
motherfucking Mexicans!
(ominous music)
Motherfucking knives
and shit.
I want every ese
motherfucking dead!
Motherfucking knives
and shit. man.
I don't know
where the fuck Franklin at.
He said he was going over to
his mama's house.
-probably at Melody's.
-You sure they cut their dicks
off. my nigga?
You see that shit?
Mookie did. He said he saw
the bodies with the coroner
over there by El Big Burrito.
-At Wabash and Stone?
-Hold on! That's goddamn
Pico-Union. nigga!
I told you to stop fucking
with them goddamn Mexicans
and the skinny fucking
motherfuckers!
I know. but I can't lose you
right now.
Mookie called Delroy's mom.
Delroy's mama
called Leon's mama.
Leon's mama tried to page him.
he wasn't answering.
so she called my mama.
Delroy and his mama
used to live with me.
He more like my little
brother than my cousin.
-And now. we gotta get 'em.
-We will get 'em.
Now we gotta kill 'em!
Hold on! Mookie called
Latisha. Latisha called Gloria.
Gloria told you.
and you just gonna what?
Go out in the street
and just shoot anybody?
-It don't make no sense!
-We'll kill all the fucking
esés. fuck 'em!
Delroy's dead.
Vic is dead.
They castrated them!
-They castrate 'em!
-They lynched 'em!
They cas...
They done lynched the nigga!
-Okay...
-Come on. Lee!
(overlapping shouting)
Nobody here seen a body!
And even if they are dead.
-we need to make a plan...
-Louie!
Get back to your
goddamn girlfriend!
-Okay...
-This is man shit!
Just find Franklin first!
Fuck Franklin!
Fine! I'll find him!
Do you need me
to do something?
No. baby. this is man shit!
All right. at least just
let us load up the plane.
and then we'll wait
for your bosses.
if that's what you want.
Do you understand
that we represent
the American Government?
♪
America.
Mm.
United States
is a pichiruchi country
who can't win a war without the
rest of the world behind it.
♪
You murdered the Indians.
you chained the blacks.
and you pissed on the vatos.
I spit on America.
♪
And your country?
It's nothing.
It is weak.
It is inconsequential.
You are like a pawn
that we sacrifice.
You play chess. or...
Nah. you're probably more
of a checkers kind of guy.
(chuckles)
-Hey!
-(speaking Spanish)
(shouting in Spanish)
Wait! No! Don't shoot!
(whistles)
♪
Hello. Reed.
(children laughing)
This isn't
what I had in mind.
You wanted back in.
(speaking Spanish)
(snoring)
(knocks on door)
Gustavo.
-Okay.
-(snorts)
(scoffs)
Mm?
(clicks tongue)
(blows landing)
(tense music)
♪
Maybe we should
go somewhere else.
Why? This is where
the shit happened.
Where the esés at?
JEROME:
They're probably asleep.
Shit. first time
I've been outside the house
before noon in a goddamn year.
Look. we just gotta
pick somebody.
-don't really matter who.
-Oh. hell no.
That shit ain't right.
KEVIN:
It ain't right?
No. what ain't right
is them killing
our motherfucking people
like animals.
We gotta send a message. right?
By killing
a bunch of old folks
and fucking kids. my nigga?
We can't let these
motherfucking wetbacks
kill our people.
then walk around
like ain't shit happened.
♪
Oh. y'all too soft.
So I'm gonna have to
do this shit myself.
-Let me out of the car. man.
-No. my nigga.
(overlapping shouts)
You ain't killing no
fucking kids. my nigga!
(pounding)
You dumb motherfuckers.
Wrap this shit up.
We out of here.
♪
(distant siren)
What the fuck
is wrong with you people?
You just gonna go out in
the street. start shooting
'cause you got a phone call?
Not just
a fucking phone call.
Mookie seen it. man.
they really dead.
So you gonna go and kill
the first Mexican you see?
That's what you do. man!
Ain't your daddy a Panther?
They hit you.
you hit them back!
You just out here
with your M-16
backing this shit up?
You the one who warned me
'bout the motherfuckers
in the first place!
They killed one
of our goddamn folks.
-all right? I overreacted!
-That's still just hearsay.
-you don't just go out there...
-No. it wasn't. man.
Mookie seen...
-What is you doing?
-Come on.
What's wrong with y'all?
We already lost two people.
and now you put
three more in jeopardy
and you know what?
I don't even know why the fuck
any of this shit even happened!
Delroy and Victor was out
there pitching on Pico-Union.
I thought we told them
to stay out of there.
I know we told them
to stay out of there
-but I can't make...
-That's the fucking job!
That's the fucking job. man!
When we tell somebody
to do some shit.
we supposed
to make sure they do it.
It was in the same place
where that Mexican bitch
gave you the phone number.
You mean to tell me
you knew somebody
who might've helped you?
Might've told you
what really happened.
you didn't think
to call her first
before going
down there fully loaded?
Nephew. I gave you the card
with the goddamn number on it.
LUCIA:
How's it going?
(speaking Spanish)
Sometimes one looks good.
but it's rotten at the core.
Sometimes it's hard to tell.
Pedro made it sound like this
whole place was just for show.
No. our farms in Mexico
are where we started.
They're our heartbeat.
our identity.
SOLEDAD:
And you don't want any
rotten onions in the basket.
For a farmer's daughter.
old habits die hard.
Mira. Lucia. I think
that you will come to feel
that you and I
are not so different.
How's that?
We are both survivors.
(Latin music)
(chuckles)
(speaking Spanish)
Tiger Fuentes?
-Gigi.
-(chuckles)
LUCIA:
She is a handful.
(speaking Spanish)
I'm fine. really.
(phone ringing)
Bueno?
FRANKLIN:
I want to talk to the woman
who sent me her phone number
a couple days ago
from down the Pico-Union.
(ominous music)
Yeah. I wanted to talk to you
about a possible business deal.
♪
Yeah.
I don't know about all that.
The reason I'm calling
is to find out
why my men were killed
yesterday.
FRANKLIN:
Murdered and mutilated.
They're dead?
♪
Are you sure?
Lady. what the fuck?
(music intensifies)
Two of men are dead.
you're asking am I sure?
I didn't know.
I hadn't heard.
Who are you?
Lucia Villanueva.
You know who
killed my people. Lucia?
LUCIA:
I have no idea.
Let me look into it.
and then maybe we can meet.
Say 2:00?
♪
Not in no Pico-Union.
What about that park
near Gower?
It's public
and not Mexican or black.
2:00.
♪
Do me a favor.
Only bring one of your people.
Will you only
bring one of yours?
Me and mine
ain't killed none of yours.
♪
I'll see you at 2:00 then.
Have the pigs' feet.
They call it
Spanish pigs' feet.
But it is a delicacy
of our culture.
We came here in good faith.
DANILO: The pigs' feet
is a national dish.
but aguardiente
is what we drink.
It is related to
the Mexican tequila and mescal.
but it is a superior. uh...
What do you call it?
-Spirit.
-You're wasting our time.
We're gonna miss the window
for our drop.
I thought you guys
were professionals.
not amateurs.
Amateurs?
You're the amateurs.
DIEGO:
It is an amateur
who allows his own man
to steal his plane
and his cocaine.
An amateur
who misses a week of product.
An amateur who arrives
with a gringo
we've never seen before
and expects us to trust him.
I came here especially
to reassure you
and to introduce you
to my new pilot.
Instead. I have been beaten.
I have been insulted...
You mouthed off.
You called our country...
(speaking Spanish)
Who do you think you are?
Talking about
our country like that.
You're right.
he shouldn't have done that.
But your man.
he insulted our country.
-So what?
-Your country is shit.
-Less than shit.
-Okay.
But my man
doesn't see it that way.
He loves his country.
Your man upset him.
That is no excuse.
You shit on our people.
Look...
He's sorry.
I'm sorry.
We're both sorry.
But if you don't
get us on our way.
we're gonna miss our drop.
and that's gonna cause
mucho problems.
I like this guy.
Maybe you should screw him.
marica.
Maybe I will.
(speaking Spanish).
If we let you go now.
you'll take twice
the weight on this trip.
To make up for what
you missed last week.
MATT: We didn't bring
enough money for that.
But we'd be happy
to take the weight.
make up
the difference next time.
There are also
some other things.
Some gifts that we need.
Two cases of Tony the Tiger
Frosted Flakes.
29 copies of Michael Jackson's
album Thriller.
A case of sheepskin condoms.
15 Cabbage Patch Dolls
for Christmas
and those fancy
Christmas lights.
Lots and lots
of those fancy lights.
And visas for my friend
and I and our families.
And also. one bodyguard
who will bring his mother
and young daughter.
-No visas.
-Yes. visas.
We want to take our wives
to Disneyland.
And our girlfriends
to Las Vegas.
Paul Anka is playing
at the Flamingo next week.
-Paul Anka?
-All right. thank you. no.
You're talking about
official government documents.
I thought
you were the government.
DIEGO:
Isn't that what you told us?
That's what he told us.
Unless you're a fucking liar.
We'll take care of the visas.
It's no problem.
Now I like him.
Maybe you should screw him.
("At the Party"
by Treacherous Three)
♪
♪ Special K!
Whoo ♪
♪ Sunshine
♪ Kool Moe Dee
all:
♪ And we're the Treacherous
♪ Treacherous.
the Treacherous Three ♪
♪ Gonna rock
from the bottom to the T-O-P ♪
♪
♪ Well.
it's a brand new beat ♪
-♪ And a brand new rhyme
-♪ Kool Moe De
-♪ Special K
-♪ And LA Sunshine
♪ Sup with that
to your ears ♪
-♪ So everybody cheer
-♪ And listen to the
♪ Number one MCs of the year
♪ You say
we tried. tried. tried ♪
♪ But now we did it.
now it's done ♪
♪ We proved it to the people
that we are number one ♪
♪ Now we're back now we're
back now we're back for more ♪
♪ Hot to give the party people
what we have in store ♪
-♪ So let's play the game
-♪ Let's play the game
Esé.
♪ It's like a lunch.
punch. munch. crunch.
♪ This is the way
we're rocking a bunch ♪
(music fades)
El Oso.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm the man
you're looking for.
Can we talk in private?
(geese honking)
Jerome tells me
they killed your uncle
a few months ago.
Sorry to hear that.
My father died
around the same time.
Nothing to do about it.
-People die.
-Yeah.
Sometimes
it don't make no sense.
Victor and Delroy were wrong.
But to kill them for standing
on a street corner was foul.
Yes it was.
My people want
this murder avenged.
A fucking mutilation?
Your friends were killed.
But there was no mutilation.
I know that doesn't
make things any better.
but there's
an even bigger problem.
The man who did this
is not just some street thug.
You know his name?
Yeah.
But he's protected.
By who?
Everyone.
The man who killed your people.
if he were touched
by you or any of your men.
you'd have an entire
army of vatos
after you
and everyone you know.
(ominous music)
Why are you here?
Because I know about
the drug you've been selling.
The hard cocaine.
I may be able
to help you sell a lot more.
Two of my men are dead.
and you're here to talk
about business?
Your men were doing business.
The man
who killed them was too.
Everything we do
is about business.
How do I tell my people
that they working
with the enemy?
I'm not the enemy.
And you are not a puppet.
♪
No promises.
What kind of business
are we talking about?
Hey. what up. Oso?
You still wrestling and shit?
Man. don't talk to him;
he's with them!
♪
Okay. that's fine.
but my people are still
gonna want to do something
about our dead men.
♪
I'll try to broker a deal
that will make us both happy.
♪
Take care.
-Hey. where they going?
-Home.
She told you who did it?
She gonna ask around.
Ask around? Man. all these
spics know each other. man.
You gotta make her tell you
who killed Delroy.
She can't tell us
what she don't know.
-Bullshit she don't know.
-She wasn't there. Kev.
She gonna find us a number.
and then we gotta do
something about it.
but we gotta wait on that!
Fuck that! These Mexicans
killed our people. your people.
-and you just tuck tail and run!
-I'm tired of listening
-to this shit. Kev!
-Shit ain't right. man!
I always knew you wasn't
built for this shit. son.
♪
(sobs)
Fuck that shit. man.
I love y'all.
Hey. come on. man!
Come back.
JEROME: Hey!
♪
(engine roaring)
So where exactly
are you planning
on getting these visas?
I don't know why
you're so pissed off.
I'm the one who got us
out of there.
Well. yeah.
by making promises
that I'm gonna have to keep.
Better that
than a bullet to the head.
Second. who says
you have to keep them?
Oh. oh. oh!
(stammering)
You think it's a good idea
to be making empty promises
to crazy Colombian
drug dealers?
Yes. they are
crazy Colombian drug dealers.
Who gives a shit
what you promise them?
Jesus Christ.
Look. from now on. just leave
the negotiating to me. okay?
No. Not when
what you're saying has them
pointing a gun at my head.
You came to me. remember?
-You needed my help?
-No. I need you to fly
the plane. Matt.
to fly the load!
Apparently that's not all!
I was in 'Nam!
There were no good guys.
And the only way
to deal with bad guys
is to be worse.
So do us both a favor. take
that stick out of your ass
and start pretending like
you got a ten-inch cock to go
along with a terminal case
of the "I-Don't-Give-a-Fucks."
And start pretending like
you are a goddamn drug dealer
before you get us both killed.
You done?
If you hear me.
I hear you.
-Then I'm done.
-Great.
(wind howling)
Drop site in ten minutes.
Clip into that harness.
I would hate
for this to be the thing
that got you killed today.
You know I fucking
love you. right?
I'm glad you're here.
It's a thrill and
a privilege. Teddy.
It is a thrill and a privilege.
(funky music)
I just can't go
to that cookhouse today.
I just can't.
Y'all niggas running around
with guns and shit.
And then expect me
to wash your dishes
and cook your rock.
Uh-uh. Just no.
Shit. Wanda could cook.
Yeah. we hear her cooking
on your rock every night.
(laughs)
You don't hear the half of it.
Hey. baby.
Auntie.
Jerome get you them studs?
Jerome? (laughs)
Jerome wouldn't know a diamond
if it bit him on the ass.
(soul music playing)
♪
Product coming in soon.
That's why I need you
in the cookhouse. Louie.
I need your car. Unc.
You bring
the shit back in one piece?
Leon. you're with me.
That's good.
FRANKLIN: You talk to Kev?
LEON: He with his family
and Delroy's mama.
He blame himself
for putting his boy to work.
I'm gone one day.
people start dying.
Kev going crazy.
I mean. I know
him and Delroy were close.
but we told them fools
"Stay out of Pico-Union."
What Kev want? Huh?
Start a war.
get us all killed?
You did
the right thing. Saint.
I mean. Kev
was way out of line.
But you know. he didn't
grow up without no daddy.
so he don't know nothing
about no rules.
Neither did you.
But you learned somehow.
Look. tomorrow we got
that big shipment coming.
So I'm gonna need you
to work the cookhouse
so we can catch up. huh?
I got you.
Hey. one more thing.
I was wrong to get in that car.
We all was.
Next time. I'll wait for you.
(suspenseful music)
♪
You dropped twice
the load we agreed on.
I know.
But that's just the way it's
gonna have to be from now on.
But it means
that you double your take. so.
It was a pleasure
to meet you. senorita.
-You too.
-All right.
♪
We have to teach our people
how to break up
the hard cocaine.
Franklin says each rock
will be about
the size of a pool ball.
We break them down
to a 1/10 of a gram each.
You think we can
trust (inaudible) to move it
after what Conejo did?
Hopefully they do
what Gabriela says.
I'll talk to Hernan.
He'll organize the women
to break the drug down.
♪
LUCIA:
What do we do about Conejo?
Guys like that
are bad for business.
stay out of his way.
Men like that
are in this for glory.
Their sons can't eat glory.
They need their fathers
to teach them how to be men.
To teach them how
to be fathers. not killers.
Yeah. but...
Truth only helps
if a man accepts it.
♪
(scoffs)
It was like
going around with a child.
Maybe he'll
get bored and quit.
Why let Pedro back in...
LUCIA: That's not true.
He's my family. Oso.
I don't have much family left.
(birds chirping)
I thought we were
supposed to meet at 6:00.
Yeah.
You always show up
an hour early?
Just something I do.
Never wondered why.
It's 'cause you're smart
and careful.
Those are qualities
that'll serve us both well.
I think.
I thought we said ten keys.
ten a pop.
Yeah. that's the money.
My customers
don't pay in large bills.
You ever hear of a bank?
You know what happens
when a black man
walks into a bank
with dirty fives and tens?
Maybe you're
using the wrong bank.
Maybe you show me
the right one.
If I do that.
maybe you could start
taking more than ten
keys a week?
Let's do a couple deals
with ten first.
Then maybe we could talk
doing some more.
Sure.
Business is only as good
as the people you work with.
You mean you work with people
who tase. interrogate.
and drug you?
And people
who have you followed.
(dramatic hip-hop music)
♪
LOUIE: And this gonna be
coming in every week now?
-Mm-hmm.
-We're gonna need a stove
-in every room.
-And more fucking cookers.
FRANKLIN:
Stoves. yeah.
I want to be careful
about who know the recipe.
So for now.
we keep the cooking in family.
Even if we
get this all rocked up.
we ain't got enough soldiers
to move it.
There ain't enough smokers
in LA for all this shit.
All y'all gotta do is cook it
up and break it down.
I'll figure out how to move it.
♪
All right. man.
ROB: Hey. man.
Hey.
With Avi gone.
the Valley's pretty dry.
You cool with me
taking a kilo of powder.
seeing if I can move it?
♪
You know somebody
hook it up?
Yeah. I've got a couple guys
who could be good for it.
All right. man. all you.
As long as
I'm fronting this shit.
we split it 60/40.
Okay. that's good by me.
both: Rad.
♪
(siren wailing in distance)
(knocks)
(ominous music)
♪
-Hey.
-Hi.
Can I come in?
Yeah. come on.
Louie and Jerome here?
Nah. we alone.
You look nice.
What?
Was it really Jerome
that made you carry
around that gun?
We're just
being careful. Mel.
So you ain't never
used a gun on anyone?
Never.
Good.
(laughs)
(knocking on door)
(knocking continues)
(knocking grows louder)
(knocking intensifies)
Mr. Wright.
Officer Wright.
How can I help you. Officer?
You see that Toyota.
parked down the block?
(ominous music)
FRANKLIN:
What about it?
It belongs
to a missing person
named Malcolm Jenkins.
Went by "Biscuit."
♪
He worked for a bail bondsman
that you recently hired.
♪
So?
Is that all you gotta say?
Nothing else to say.
WRIGHT:
You want to explain the car?
FRANKLIN:
Maybe it broke down.
Maybe his friend
picked him up.
maybe he took the bus.
Maybe somebody
stole the motherfucker
and left it there.
I don't know.
Bullshit.
I don't know
what you want from me. man.
I'm just in my crib.
watching TV.
See. you think you're smarter
than everybody else.
But you're not.
You see. I'm gonna make sure
that the truth surfaces
with this shit.
Until then.
stay the fuck
away from me and mine.
♪
You understand?
That all?
♪
FRANKLIN:
Where are the bodies?
PEACHES:
Gone.
♪
FRANKLIN: You didn't think
to check if they had a car?
I knew it was there when I
felt the keys in his pocket.
What am I supposed to do
about that? Steal it?
Get my fingerprints
all over it?
Them men dead and gone.
They won't be the last.
Just do your job. Saint.
I'll do mine.
♪
(tense music)
(radio chatter)
Okay. move out.
Clear 'em out!
Let's go.
♪
Move!
Let's go. let's go!
Get them all out of here now.
♪
I ain't moving!
I ain't going!
(shouting)
(distorted whoosh)
♪
(blows landing)
Captioned by Captionmax
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-